Council of Europe Adult Education Collection
Council of Europe Adult Education Collection
1966-1974
Council of Europe.
0.3 linear ft.
Reports from various Council of Europe committees relating to adult and continuing education
2668682
Biographical History
"Founded in 1949, the Council of Europe seeks to develop throughout Europe common and democratic principles based on the European Convention on Human Rights and other reference texts on the protection of individuals."
[from the Council's website, http://www.coe.int/T/e/Com/about_coe]
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Council of Europe Adult Education Collection consists of reports from several different Council committees relating to adult and continuing education.
Arrangement of the Collection
Reports are arranged in alphabetical order by title.
Related Material
has numerous collections of both individuals and organizations, relating to adult education. Please refer to for a complete listing. The library's circulating collection also has substantial adult education holdings; please refer to for a complete listing of cataloged items.
Subject and Genre Headings
Adult education; Council of Europe. Committee for Higher Education and Research; Council of Europe. Committee for Out-of-School Education.; Council of Europe. Committee for Out-of-School Education and Cultural Development.; Council of Europe. Council for Cultural Co-operation.; Adult education -- Audio-visual aids.; Adult education -- Research.; Adult education -- Study and teaching.; Degrees, Academic -- Research.; Occupational training -- Europe.; Television in education.; Vocational training -- Europe.; Reports.; Adult educators.; Research.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Transfer from circulating collection.
Inventory
- Reports
  - Adult education theory and practice, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Conceptual and technical problems of long-range educational planning, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Equivalence of diplomas, degrees and certificates, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Evaluation des systemes multi-media, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Feasibility study in the collection of adult education statistics, 1974 (Box 1)
  - International exchange of television programmes for schools: Legal and economic problems, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Polyvalent vocational training, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Recension de recherches sur les media audiovisuels pour adultes, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Le role d l'enseignement par correspondance dans les systemes de formation multi-media, 1974 (Box 1)